<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PERSONAL PROJECTS on Alejandro Moya</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PERSONAL PROJECTS on Alejandro Moya</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prince of Persia&#39;s Time Rewind Recreation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/princeofpersia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/princeofpersia/</guid>
      <description>As a big fan of Prince of Persia games, I always wanted to program my own time rewind implementation, so I implemented the core mechanics of Prince of Persia in Unity and then programmed a system to rewind character controllers, AI behaviors, animations, camera, UI, hazards and more. You can find the source code here.&#xA;The Time Rewind System The time rewind implementation uses a circular stack to store the values of the mutable variables every frame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Finite State Machine Library</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/hfsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/hfsm/</guid>
      <description>A hierarchical finite state machine library implemented in C#. The GitHub repository is setup as a Unity package, but the source code does not depend on Unity packages and can be used in any C# application. This library is open source and you can check the source code on my GitHub repository. Its features are:&#xA;Class based architecture. State machines and states are implemented inheriting from StateMachine and State classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smash Bros. x Among Us Prototype</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/smashbros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/smashbros/</guid>
      <description>Created the core mechanics of a platformer fighter like Smash Bros. in Unity. Then, I added Crewmate from Among Us as a playable character. I programmed all the prototype&amp;rsquo;s features and created all the art assets (3D models, textures, animations and VFX) from scratch except for the background video. The only assets I used from the original games were some of the SFX you can hear in the trailer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Pizza</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/christmaspizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/christmaspizza/</guid>
      <description>Puzzle videogame with golf &amp;amp; scarf physics. Created in Core Games Engine as a submission for the Core Game Creator challenge. The game was awarded with one of the two 3rd place prizes.&#xA;My contributions were:&#xA;All the source code except for the cinematic camera movement at the end used Cinematic shot by standardcombo) . Art and music assets kitbashed from the engine&amp;rsquo;s assets except for the Gingerbread house (created by Stormhawk).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
